Mama! Mama!
ماما، ماما
Minister Perospero...
بيروسبيرو-ساما
I can't believe it...
...هذا لا يصدق
Mama's back to normal...
لقد عادت ماما إلى طبيعتها
Pudding made such an extraordinary cake...
يا لها من كعكة التي أعددتها يا بودينغ
I've never seen her so content. Lick.
لم أرها بهذه السعادة من قبل-بيرورين
Mama! You're our captain! I need to brief you on the current situation.
أنتِ قبطانتنا يا ماما، لذا عليّ إخبارك بالوضع الراهن
First of all, Bege should still be in the area...
أولًا، ما زال طاقم بيجي في الأرجاء
I'm so happy...
يا لسعادتي
She's not listening at all...
إنّها لا تسمعني
Is that...?!
هل تلك؟
Hey, that's not it!
ليست هي
That's not the Straw Hats' ship!
تلك ليست سفينة طاقم قبعة القش
What?!
ماذا تقول؟
That's the Sun Pirates' ship!
إنّها سفينة طاقم قراصنة الشمس
No way! It took a direct hit!
محال، لقد تعرّضت لقصفٍ مباشر
Did they switch?!
متى بدلوها؟
In that case, where did the Straw Hats go?!
أين ذهب طاقم قبعة القش إذًا؟
Hurry, Wadatsumi!
أسرع يا واداتسومي
Get as far as possible!
خذهم بعيدًا
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
This is the legendary ship that Fisher Tiger built!
إنّها السفينة الأسطورية التي بناها فيشر تايغر
I'm sure!
لا يهم
All right!
مفهوم
Hurry up! We don't have time!
أسرع، فالوقت يداهمنا
What?! What?!
ماذا؟ ماذا؟
He's gonna eat us!
سيلتهمنا
Be patient.
تحلّوا بالصبر
What the?!
ما الذي حدث؟
Where are we?!
أين نحن؟
We're in Wadatsumi's mouth!
نحن داخل فم واداتسومي
Let's escape!
لنهرب
They're in the water!
إنّهم تحت الماء
I wondered what I saw. It must have been the Giant Monk's hand!
كنت أتساءل عمّا رأيته مسبقًا، أكانت يد ذلك الراهب العملاق؟
All ships! Come about 180 degrees!
إلى كل السفن، استديروا بسرعة
I won't let you get away, you damned fishman!
لن تفلت منّا أيها البرمائي اللعين
Hot Sea...
طربيد
Torpedoes!
البحر الساخن
It's too hot!
حارٌ جدًّا
There it is! Straw Hat's ship!
إنّها سفينة طاقم قبعة القش
Wadakichi!
واداكشي
Fire! Sink Straw Hat's ship!
أطلقوا، اغرقوا سفينة طاقم قبعة القش
Just go, you guys!
اذهبوا يا رفاق
Straw Hat! I was a bad guy on Fishman Island...
قبعة القش، لقد ارتكبتُ أفعالًا شنيعة بحقكم على جزيرة البرمائيين
I'm sorry!
المعذرة
But after that, Boss Jinbe still let me join him... I-I'm so grateful!
ورغم ما فعلته، إلّا أنّ الزعيم جينبي احتواني، أنا ممتن له
That bastard...
ذلك الوغد
Get out of my way, you blasted umibozu !
ابتعد يا قرد البحر
Wadatsumi!
واداتسومي
Since the boss told us he wanted to join the Straw Hats,
منذ اللحظة التي أخبرنا بها الزعيم ...عن رغبته بالانضمام إلى طاقم قبعة القش
we all decided!
قررنا ما سنفعله
Mama will kill anyone who tries to leave.
ماما ستقتل أي شخص يحاول المغادرة
So we only have one option...
...بعبارة أخرى، ما سنفعله هو
You want us to serve as Captain Jinbe's shield and die instead?!
نضحي بأنفسنا لحماية القبطان جينبي؟
We can't all die here! Someone has to tell the story!
لا فائدة من موتنا جميعًا هنا يجب أن ينجو أحدنا ليروي قصتنا البطولية
Yeah, you're right.
أتفق معك
I won't fault anyone for running away! Those who follow me should be prepared for anything!
لن ألوم أحدكم إن أراد الهرب لكن من يودّ أن يتبعني فليستعد لتحمّل العواقب مهما كانت
We won't let them get in the way of Jinbe's new beginning!
لن ندعهم يعيقون بداية رحلة جينبي الجديدة
We all made up our minds!
لقد حسمنا أمرنا
Get down, Wadatsumi!
تراجع يا واداتسومي
Aladine! You guys!
...علاء الدين، أيها الرفاق
Jinbe! Straw Hats! Get out of here!
اهرب أنت وطاقم قبعة القش يا جينبي
We wish you a safe voyage!
نرجو لكم رحلةً آمنة
Let's go, men!
هيّا بنا يا رفاق
Luffy...
لوفي
Flooding is a sailing ship's weakness. Be sure to drain the water quickly...
تسرب المياه في السفينة هو نقطة ضعفها لذا أصرفوا المياه بسرعة
or the ship will be heavy and slow.
وإلّا ستكون السفينة ثقيلة وبطيئة
After that, you should patch up the sails in order to properly catch the wind
وقوموا باستبدال الأشرعة المثقوبة للاستفادة من اتجاه الرياح
and escape as fast as you can!
وتقدموا بأقصى سرعة ممكنة
It'll still take several hours to escape this territory!
سيستغرق الأمر منكم عدّة ساعات للخروج من هذا الإقليم
What are you saying, Jinbe?! Why are you telling us this?!
ما الذي تقوله يا جينبي؟ لِمَ تشرح هذه الأمور لنا؟
Luffy...
...لوفي
I can't leave them behind!
لا يمكنني التخلّي عنهم
Okay, I got it!
حسنًا، فهمت
Then... we'll stay, too!
سنبقى نحن أيضًا
They're guarding the rear to cover you!
سأحميكم من الخلف ليتسنى لكم الهرب
If you're cornered by the flagship's fleet now, escape will be impossible!
في الوضع الراهن، إن ظلّت السفينة الرئيسية وسفن الأسطول خلفنا مباشرة، فلن نتمكن من الهرب
Please allow me...
...دعني أتولّى
to bring up the rear!
مهمة حماية السفينة من الخلف
We'll pull it off and come back alive!
سأنفذ هذه المهمة وأعود
Don't forget, Jinbe!
لا تنسَ يا جينبي
I am your captain now!
أنا قبطانك الآن
Jinn-uinely Enraged Cleave!
قطع الشر
I won't stop the ship, but...
لن أوقف السفينة
I'll wait for you in Wano! You better be there!
سننتظرك في بلاد وانو، تعال مهما كلّف الأمر
Luffy!
لوفي
You have my gratitude!
أنا ممتن لك
Jinbe!
جينبي
Don't die no matter what!
إيّاك أن تموت
He's still alive? That Straw Hat brat?
أما يزال ذلك الشقي قبعة القش حيًّا؟
Y-Yes, he's alive for now...
...أجل، لا يزال حيًّا حاليًّا
but I just got a report that my siblings have him cornered at Cacao Island.
لكن وردني اتصال للتو يفيد بأنّ إخوتي يقاتلونه الآن على جزيرة الكاكاو
He has nowhere to run!
لا مفرّ له
I’m going if he’s still alive.
بما أنّه لم يمت، فسأذهب إلى هناك
Hurry, Golden Tree Frog!
أسرع يا ضفدع الحلوى
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat...
استعد لملاقاة مصيرك يا قبعة القش
I'll steal your soul and make some fearsome homies out of it!
سأسلب روحك وأجعل منها أحد أقوى الهوميز الذين يعملون تحت إمرتي
We survived...
نجونا بأعجوبة
Life isn't all bad. Let's get away quietly.
لربما الأوقات الصعبة لا تدوم، لنهرب بسلام الآن
I'm worried about Germa-rero...
أنا قلق على الجيرما-ريرو
Shut up!
اخرس
Burn!
احترق
Heat Cross!
قبضة الرياح الساخنة
Are you okay, Aladine?!
هل أنت بخير يا علاء الدين؟
Jinbe! You're returning to us?!
جينبي، هل عدت إلينا؟
No, I'm still a member of the Straw Hat crew.
كلا، ما زلت عضوًا في طاقم قبعة القش
I'm just staying behind to protect my captain!
لكنني بقيت هنا لإنقاذ قبطاني
Come on now!
...بحقك
You're underestimating us!
أنت تستهين بنا
That's not it, Brother.
لا تفكر في الأمر بهذه الطريقة
Everyone has to survive...
...يجب أن تنجو جميعًا
so you can give me a proper send-off!
ليتسنى لكم توديعي
I know your strength better than anyone!
أدرك مدى قوتكم أكثر من أي شخص آخر
Let's make good use of it to ensure that the Straw Hats escape!
لنستخدم هذه القوة لمساعدة طاقم قبعة القش على الهرب
Those bastards!
أولئك الأوغاد
It's a maelstrom!
إنّها دوامة
Brook! Hurry and get the Sunny as far as you can!
بروك، أبعد سفينة الساني عن هذه الدوامة بأقصى سرعة
Understood!
مفهوم
When fishmen get serious, we can change the current of the ocean itself!
حين يُطلق البرمائيين العنان لقوتهم فإنهم قادرين على تغيير تيار البحر
Amazing!
مذهل
The sea is...
...البحر
The current that the fishmen generated is carrying the Sunny away!
التيار الذي أحدثه البرمائيين يدفع سفينة الساني بعيدًا
Jinbe...
جينبي
Jinbe is covering Straw Hat Luffy as he sails away!
قبعة القش لوفي يُبحر بعيدًا في ظل حماية جينبي لسفينته من الخلف
Our fleet is completely tied down,
...أسطولنا عالقٌ في الدوامة
and we'll soon lose track of their ship!
وسنفقد أثر سفينتهم قريبًا
That's right! Go, Straw Hat!
أجل، انطلق يا قبعة القش
Why are you cheering him on?
يبدو أنّك تدعمه
Ah... that's because Straw Hat is a prime candidate.
أجل، لأنّ قبعة القش هو أحد المرشحين
For what?
المرشحين بماذا؟
Stussy... you know about the Worst Generation, don't you?
ستوسي، ألا تعرفين الجيل الأسوأ؟
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law.
جراح الموت؛ ترافلغار لاو
Basil Hawkins "The Magician."
الساحر؛ باسيل هوكينز
"Red Flag" X Drake.
الراية الحمراء؛ ديس دريك
"Roar of the Sea" Scratchmen Apoo.
زئير البحر؛ سكراتشمان آبو
Capone "Gang" Bege.
كابوني غانغ بيجي
Jewelry Bonney "The Glutton."
الشرهة؛ جيورلي بوني
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
الراهب المجنون؛ عروج
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
يوستاس كابتن كيد
"Soldier of Slaughter" Killer.
آلة القتل؛ كيلر
Marshall D. "Blackbeard" Teach.
اللحية السوداء؛ مارشال دي تيتش
And...
...وأيضًا
"Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy.
قبعة القش؛ مونكي دي لوفي
I'm certain...
:إليكِ ما أعتقده
that someone from this so-called Worst Generation...
...«هؤلاء الذين يُطلق عليهم اسم «الجيل الأسوأ
will rise up and become the next pirate king!
سيغدو أحدهم قريبًا ملك القراصنة الجديد
I see. So Pedro...
...فهمت، بيدرو قد
is dead.
مات
My name is Pedro! Please help me...
اسمي بيدرو، أرجوكم ساعدونا
Get them treated now... or they'll die!
إن لم نعالجهما الآن، فسيموتان
The world needs them!
العالم ينتظرهما
Those two...
...يجب ألّا ندعهما
can never...
...مهما كلّف الأمر، مهما كلّف الأمر
be allowed to die!
أن يموتان
It's because he came to rescue me...
لقد مات لأنّه أتى لإنقاذي
I don't think this was where he was supposed to die...
لم يكن من المفترض أن تموت في هذا المكان
It's all right. It's all right, Sanji!
لا بأس، لا بأس يا سانجي
This was Pedro's own choice!
بيدرو جاء إلى هنا بملء إرادته
Please don't blame yourself! Sanji!
لا تلم نفسك يا سانجي
You guys saved the Mokomo Dukedom, so he wanted to repay the favor!
أنت ورفاقك أنقذتم دوقية موكومو لذا أردنا أن نردّ لكم المعروف
Besides, if it weren't for Pedro, we would've all died back there!
لولا بيدرو، لكنّا جميعًا في عداد الموتى آنذاك
So...
...لذا
just... thank him.
اشكره بدلًا من لوم نفسك
This is for the best!
لأنّ هذا ما كان يريده
I know what kind of man he was.
أعرف معدنه كرجل حق المعرفة
♪ Soul Pocus... ♪
♪ كلمات الروح ♪
♪ with deep doubt ♪
♪ ...يتردد صداها ♪
♪ The tide guides the way... pulling the ship away... ♪
♪ على متن السفينة التي تشق عباب المحيط ♪
♪ from the sea consumed by a fearsome fray! ♪
♪ مبتعدةً عن بحر المعركة ♪
It's a cotton candy flurry!
ثلج حلوى القطن
We must be close to the border.
هذا يعني أننا اقتربنا من حدود الإقليم
Just a bit further and we'll be out of Big Mom's territory!
أوشكنا على الخروج من إقليم بيغ مام
♪ Mama’s back! ♪
♪ ماما عادت إلى طبيعتها ♪
♪ Flower! ♪
♪ زهرة ♪
♪ I'm sure they faced great adversity! ♪
♪ رغم الأوضاع الصعبة ♪
♪ Yet the flowers and trees sing brightly! ♪
♪ إلّا أنّ الأزهار والأشجار تغني بسعادة ♪
♪ And they seduce us so sweetly! ♪
♪ :وتسحرنا بأدائها الجميل لأغنية ♪
♪ Soul Pocus! ♪
♪ كلمات الروح ♪
♪ It's all the plan of our greedy Mama, a grand show for all! ♪
♪ مؤامرة ماما الجشعة والماكرة ♪
♪ The fairy-tale prince! ♪
♪ ...أمير الحكايات الخيالية ♪
♪ The beautiful princess! ♪
♪ والأميرة الجميلة ♪
♪ Shoved into a loveless puppet show! ♪
♪ يتم التلاعب بهما في مسرحية عرائس حيث لا ينجذبان إلى بعضهما ♪
♪ Like a hard heart lured in by a nectar’s sweet smell! ♪
♪ حتى الرحيق الحلو الذي يجذبنا بنكهته لا يخلو من الخبث ♪
♪ If there's anything in this world worse than sweetness, it's hard to tell! ♪
♪ لا شيء في هذا العالم أكثر رعبًا من حلاوة يسيل لها اللعاب ♪
♪ Hidden motivations and misconceptions... ♪
♪ دوافع خفية وسوء فهم ♪
♪ make you play your role or you'll risk your soul... ♪
♪ مسرحية قذرة كادت تودي بحياتنا للتهلكة ♪
♪ Join and get candy! ♪
♪ حين قدومنا كانت الحلوى تنتظرنا ♪
♪ Leave and it’s the guillotine! ♪
♪ وحين مغادرتنا كانت المقصلة تنتظرنا ♪
♪ Who will win this thrilling fight? ♪
♪ من الذي ظفر بالنصر في المعركة يا تُرى؟ ♪
Fishman Karate Secret Technique:
كاراتيه البرمائيين السري
Vagabond Drill!
الثقب الأوحد
Hang in there!
اصمدوا
Once Luffy and the others get out of the territory, we can go too!
حالما يخرج لوفي والآخرين من الإقليم، سنغادر نحن أيضًا
Hey, what happened to the Straw Hats?
أنتم، أين طاقم قبعة القش؟
There's been no word from our pursuit unit!
لم نسمع خبرًا من وحدة المطاردة
I think they lost them!
يبدو أنّهم فقدوا أثرهم
Idiot! Once they cross the border, we won't be able to catch up!
أيها الأحمق، لن نستطيع اللحاق بهم إن عبروا الحدود
Pudding, like usual, you must seduce him with your acting skills.
كالعادة يا بودينغ، استخدمي مهاراتك في التمثيل لجعله يقع في غرامك
That's no problem, Mama!
مهمة سهلة يا ماما
You're like a puppet, Pudding.
أنتِ دميتي الصغيرة يا بودينغ
Ready to play out my will.
دميتي التي استخدمها وقتما أشاء
Mama... I'm not a puppet...
ماما، أنا لست دمية
Let's get married tomorrow.
لنتزوج غدًا
Yeah, right... Like all the others, once he finds out who I really am, he'll...
أحمق، ستتصرف مثل البقية حالما ترى هيئتي الحقيقية
Even if you're my daughter, I can't deny that's creepy...
رغم أنني والدتكِ لكنّي أرى هذه العين تثير الاشمئزاز
She's a monster!
إنّها وحش
"Let's get married!"
«لنتزوج»
You sound exactly like him!
تبدين مثله تمامًا
So creepy!
مخيفة للغاية
Look! She's a freak!
انظروا إلى عين الوحش
Don't do it!
توقفوا
No one could ever really love me.
لن يحبني أحد
I'm just an ugly freak.
فأنا مجرد وحش بشع
Like all the others, once you find out who I really am...
...مثل البقية، حالما ترى هيئتي الحقيقية
Take a good look, Sanji... at my creepy...
...أمعن النظر يا سانجي... إلى ما سيُخيفك
third eye!
عيني الثالثة
What a beautiful eye!
يا لها من عينٍ جميلة
All right! Let's start baking!
حسنًا، لنبدأ بإعداد الكعكة
I'm glad that you were the one to play my fiancée, Pudding-chan!
لكنني سعيد بأنّ من لعبت دور خطيبتي هي بودينغ-تشان
Pudding-chan!
بودينغ-تشان
H-Hey, Sanji...
...يا سانجي
...-san...
سان-
could you do me a favor?!
أيمكنك أن تحقق لي طلبًا؟
Oh...? Pudding-chan?!
ماذا؟ بودينغ-تشان؟
You said that you wanted... to ask me a favor...
...الطلب الأخير الذي تريدينه منّي
What was it?
ما هو؟
Brother Peros, come in! Where's Mama now?!
أجبني يا أخي الكبير بيروس، أين ماما الآن؟
Damn!
سحقًا
Minister Mont d'Or! We got a call from Cacao Island!
مونت دور-ساما، وردنا اتصال من جزيرة الكاكاو
It looks like a territorial sea slug reported from the border!
يبدو أنّه ما زال لدينا بعض رخويات البحر عند حدود الإقليم
It's too late!
لقد فات الأوان
It signaled an alert of a passing ship! The Straw Hats have left the territory!
وقد بعثت تقريرًا يُفيد بخروج سفينة طاقم قبعة القش من الإقليم
Return to your ships, Germa 66! Mission accomplished!
عودوا إلى سفنكم يا جيرما 66، أُنجزت المهمة
Roger!
عُلم
Germa is retreating!
قوّات جيرما تنسحب
Don't let them go!
لا تدعوهم يهربون
Catch them!
الحقوا بهم
I never wanted to see my big brother on his back, defeated.
لم أكن أودّ رؤيتك خاسرًا ومستلقيًا على ظهرك هكذا
Brûlée.
بروليه
You fell on your back on purpose, didn't you? You were on your stomach first.
لِمَ نهضت وسقطت على ظهرك؟ ألم تكن مستلقيًا على بطنك في البداية؟
I wonder...
...أتساءل لماذا
But Brûlée...
...لكن يا بروليه
all those stories about how I never lie down...
الأقاويل المتداولة عن أنّ ظهري لم ...يلمس الأرض طيلة حياتي
they're not true.
مجرد كذبة
Yeah, I know. I've seen you through the mirrors.
أجل، أعلم ذلك، فقد كنت أشاهدك عبر المرايا
You've been playing the role...
...لقد تظاهرت بأنّك
of the perfect unbeatable man...
رجل مثالي لا يُقهر، صحيح؟
for our sake.
وذلك من أجلنا
Katakuri, if you just hid that mouth, you'd have friends.
كاتاكوري، ستحظى بأصدقاء إن أخفيت فمك هذا
Don't want 'em! I am who I am! I'll just beat up anyone that laughs!
لن أفعل، فهذه طبيعتي، وسأبرح ضربًا كل من يضحك عليّ
A pelican eel!
إنّه الإنقليس
He's a pelican eel!
إنّ الإنقليس قادم
I'll kick their asses!
سأبرحكم ضربًا
Oh, no!
مصيبة
Hurry!
أسرعوا
How could this happen?
ما الذي حدث لها؟
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
What's the matter?
ما الخطب؟
What?!
ماذا؟
This is serious! Brûlée is badly injured!
مصيبة، إنّ بروليه مصابة بشدّة
Brûlée!
بروليه
What... happened?
ما الذي... حدث؟
It's nothing...
لا شيء
No, it's not nothing! Tell me! What happened?!
،لا يمكن أن يكون هذا لا شيء أخبريني، ما الذي حدث؟
Those guys you beat up earlier came back for revenge, Katakuri!
أولئك الأشخاص الذين ضربتهم أتوا للانتقام يا كاتاكوري
Revenge?! On my sister?!
انتقام؟ من أختي؟
Why?! Why did she have to be the one to get hurt?!
لماذا؟ لماذا اختاروا الانتقام بالاعتداء على أختي؟
Big Brother...
...أخي
It doesn't... hurt at all...
هذا لا يؤلم إطلاقًا
You're fine just the way you are, Big Brother.
مظهرك جميل كما أنت
You fool! I'm...
...يا لحماقتي
Brûlée got hurt because of me...
...تأذّت بروليه بسببي
I was too naive!
كنتُ متساهلًا للغاية
Here comes Katakuri!
ها قد أتيت يا كاتاكوري
We've been expecting you.
كنا ننتظرك
Huh? What's that around your neck?!
ماذا؟ ما هذا الذي حول عنقك؟
How dare you scar my sister's face?!
كيف تجرؤون على تشويه وجه أختي؟
I'll never lower my guard again!
لن أتساهل مجدّدًا
I'll teach you all what true fear is!
سأجعلهم يخافون من مدى مثاليتي
Brûlée...
بروليه
How's Straw Hat?
ما الذي حدث لقبعة القش؟
I'm sure you'll think "That's a relief" when you hear.
إن أخبرتك، فستغمرك السعادة بلا شك
Can you see the future, too?
أيمكنكِ رؤية المستقبل أيضًا؟
He just made it out of our territory.
لقد خرج للتو من الإقليم
But I won't forgive him...
لن أسامحه ما حييت
after what he put my big brother through!
فقد جعلك بهذه الحالة العصيبة
I knew it.
كما توقعت
Luffy and the others made it out of the territory. Let's retreat!
غادر لوفي والآخرين الإقليم، لننسحب
Germa 66, withdraw!
لننسحب يا قوّات جيرما 66
Fire! Fire! Fire! Don’t let Germa get away!
أطلقوا، أطلقوا، لا تسمحوا لجيرما بالهرب
Here she comes...
ها قد أتت
It's Mama!
إنّها ماما
♪ Soul Pocus! ♪
♪ كلمات الروح ♪
♪ The selfish excuses you make... ♪
♪ كلمات أنانية ♪
♪ are useless when you’re tempted by a sweet cake! ♪
♪ ...حين تجذبك رائحة كعكة حلوة ♪
♪ You should've accounted for what they’d take! ♪
♪ عليك أن تسأل عمّا يريدونه مقابلها ♪
♪ There is nothing to gain! ♪
♪ إن قالوا لك لن نجني مقابلها شيئًا ♪
♪ Give up a treat or be tricked in vain! ♪
♪ فهل ستنطلي خدعتهم عليك وتأخذ الحلوى؟ ♪
♪ Is there anything in this world worse than sweetness' pain? ♪
♪ لا شيء في هذا العالم أكثر رعبًا من حلاوة يسيل لها اللعاب ♪
♪ The Soul Pocus... ♪
♪ كلمات الروح ♪
♪ of our selfish... ♪
♪ ...الأنانية ♪
♪ Mama! ♪
♪ ماما ♪
♪ Will you give up your vitality... ♪
♪ هل ستعطوني سنوات من أعماركم أو تموتون؟ ♪
♪ Soul Pocus! ♪
♪ كلمات الروح ♪
♪ It's our queen's... ♪
♪ ...إنّها أغنية ♪
♪ song! ♪
♪ الملكة ♪
Life or death?
حياة أو موت؟
Shielded by the efforts of the Sun Pirates, Germa 66, and those who sacrificed everything,
بفضل طاقم قراصنة الشمس وجيرما 66 بالإضافة إلى أولئك الذين لقوا حتفهم
the Straw Hat crew finally escaped Emperor Big Mom's territory.
خرج طاقم قبعة القش من إقليم الامبراطورة بيغ مام أخيرًا
Hey...
...أنتم
Should I prepare a meal?
أتريدون طعامًا؟
A meal?
...طعام
Food!
طعام
Sanji's cooking!
طهو سانجي
I'm actually famished!
أنا جائع فعلًا
I'm starving!
أتضوّر جوعًا
It's safe, free, and delicious!
آمن ومجاني ولذيذ
Sanji's cooking!
طهو سانجي
Did something happen while I was gone?
هل حدث شيء أثناء فترة غيابي؟
Meanwhile, in the East Blue...
وفي هذه الأثناء، في الأزرق الشرقي
Isn't my meal ready yet?!
ألم يجهز الطعام بعد؟
Hey, come on!
هيّا، ما الخطب؟
Owner Zeff! Let's just kick them out!
أيها المالك زيف، دعنا نطردهم
Why do we have to serve them?
لِمَ نقدّم الطعام إليهم؟
They're criminals!
إنّهم أعداؤنا
I'll cook, so just be quiet!
سأطهو لهم بنفسي، لذا اخرسوا
Hurry up and bring the food!
أحضروا الطعام بسرعة
They're pushing their luck!
يا لبجاحتهم
Food! Food! Food! Food!
طعام، طعام، طعام، طعام
Okay, okay.
فهمت، فهمت
No matter the time of day, everyone still gets hungry.
مهما كان الوقت، الجميع يشعرون بالجوع
No matter who they might be, everyone still gets hungry.
حتّى لو كانوا أعداءك، الجميع يشعرون بالجوع
Now, dig in!
والآن، تفضلوا
– I'll feed anyone who is hungry!
سأطعم أي شخص يشعر بالجوع
– We can talk later!
وسنتحدث بعد ذلك
Puffs Island
جزيرة المعجنات
Cacao Island
جزيرة الكاكاو
The Ocean-Going Restaurant (Baratie)
المطعم البحري باراتي
JUST ONE LAST THING...
...أريدك أن تحقق لي طلبًا
I WANNA ASK YOU A FAVOR...!
...طلب واحد للمرة الأخيرة
THANK YOU AND...
...شكرًا لك